YOUN SOO LIM

(604) 364-8470 yslim.bcit@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/younsoo-lim

Front-end Development

HTML. CSS

JavaScript, jQuery React, Next.js, WordPress

MySQL, MongoDB

UI/UX Design

Graphic Design

Digital Media

Figma

InDesign

Audition

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES



Creative and Skillful Web Development Student at BCIT

Passionate about front-end development and UX/UI design. I am excited to bring my creativity and marketing expertise to digital design and development through my previous professional experience in design and manufacturing.

PROJECTS

MyLandlord | Next.js, React, React UI

SEPTEMBER 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

Rating website that offers information for residents looking for an ideal landlord

- Created prototypes and mockups, managed brand quality consistency and designed high-quality graphic images.
- Collaborated with back-end developers, full-stack students, on improving usability.
- Created user-friendly web pages by using markup languages, such as React, Next.js.

reVamp | Next.js, React

JANUARY 2021 - MAY 2021

App that helps users repurpose old clothes and reduce fast fashion waste

- Contributed to all stages of development, including planning, testing, and coding.
- Constructed a user-interactive site architecture.
- Built reusable and scalable code and components.

irl_Dater | Figma, HTML, CSS, jQuery

JANUARY 2021 - MAY 2021

Mobile dating app that enables customers to meet the perfect someone while having fun

- Collected, researched, investigated and evaluated user requirements.
- Provided an exceptional user experience through intuitive application design.
- Designed and developed a marketing website for the application.

SKILLS

Visual design and product design

Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop,

Prototyping, wireframing, user flows, mockups

Adobe Premiere Pro, After Effects,

Trend analysis and user research

Adaptability

Problem-solving

Self-learning

Leadership and team management

Time management and prioritization

Collaboration

Communication and presentation

EDUCATION

▶ Digital Design and Development | Diploma —

British Columbia Institute of Technology, Vancouver, BC SEPTEMBER 2020 – MAY 2022

• Developed a solid foundation in designing, developing, and creating interactive, dynamic, immersive social and online applications across a multi-platforms.

Global Fashion Management | Master of Professional Studies —

Fashion Institute of Technology. New York, USA

AUGUST 2011 — DECEMBER 2012

 Be prepared for top management and leadership positions in the international fashion industry as an emerging executive.

Visual Presentation and Exhibit Design | Associate in Applied Science —

Fashion Institute of Technology, New York, USA

AUGUST 2000 - MAY 2002

• Developed skill sets to work in exhibition design, retail design, product displays, special events, screen and stage design, and brand environments.

Fashion Design | Bachelor's Degree of Fine Art —

Ewha Womans University, Seoul, Korea

MARCH 1995 – FEBRUARY 1999

• Educated in fashion and related businesses as a highly creative and professional individual with expert knowledge.

PERIENCE

R&D Senior Team Manager — Hansae Fashion Worldwide,

Seoul, Korea

MAY 2018 - OCTOBER 2019

- Led a Design Team of nine members. Trained members, provided design direction, and solved problems.
- Assisted team members in developing their skills and growing in their roles.

R&D Senior Team Manager — Pan Pacific,

Seoul, Korea

OCTOBER 2014 - MAY 2018

- Planned, created, and presented knit performance and women's wear for American and European buyers.
- Designed clothes with solid brand identities based on understanding customers' needs and marketing objectives.

LANGUAGES

English Full professional proficiency

Korean Native proficiency

Japanese Limited working proficiency

1/2

YOUN SOO **Lim**

(604) 364-8470 yslim.bcit@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/younsoo-lim



Creative and Skillful Web Development Student at BCIT

Passionate about front-end development and UX/UI design. I am excited to bring my creativity and marketing expertise to digital design and development through my previous professional experience in design and manufacturing.

EXPERIENCE

Merchandiser − 2 and 1, MU Sports,

Tokyo, Japan

MAY 2014 — OCTOBER 2014

- Planned and coordinated the international shipment of goods.
- Communicated and negotiated with shippers, agents, buyers, and vendors.

R&D Senior Designer / Assistant Manager — Hansae Fashion Worldwide,

Seoul, Korea

APRIL 2006 - JULY 2011

- Planned, created, and presented knit performance and women's wear for American and European buyers.
- Designed clothes with solid brand identities based on understanding customers' needs and marketing objectives.

Technical Designer — Marc Ecko Enterprises,

New York, USA

SEPTEMBER 2003 — SEPTEMBER 2005

- Created urban-style men's and women's wear tech packs in a start-up brand.
- Collaborated with designers, providing technical adjustments and supporting the design process.

♦ Assistant Visual Merchandiser − Bloomingdale's,

New York, USA

AUGUST 2002 - APRIL 2003

- Supported stock sell-through by creating a visual appeal for customers in the store.
- Proactively managed workloads and deadlines and communicated trade-offs.

AWARDS

Summa Cum Laude (Dean's List)

Awarded by Fashion Institute of Technology in 2002.

Honourable Mention

Awarded an Honorable Mention for the design of a centerpiece for the UN Plaza Ballroom's "Salute to the Stars" event in 2002.

Magna Cum Laude (Dean's list)

Awarded by Ewha Womans University in 1999.